DHRUV PATEL

Automation Architecture

T+91 6353284679 ☑ dnp176@gmail.com







Profile Statement

An enthusiastic java developer that you can rely on, I have strong advance knowledge and 2+ years of industry and freelancing experience in the computer program development team. I am proficient in clearly explaining complex development concepts to a variety of audiences.

Education

B.Tech Computer Engineering

Sankalchand Patel University 2022

CGPA: 8.8

H.S.C

GSHEB 2018

60%

S.S.C

GSHEB 2016

66%

Work Experience

Software Developer

Freelancing / May 2020 –May 2021

Developed and customize software for diverse client base. Successfully generated back-end programming utilizing Java, Spring MVC, Hibernate framework. Using JSP for front-end, html and javascript. Build REST full API with MySQL database.

Intern Software Developer

Rainstreamweb | May 2021 -August 2022

Developed and customize software for diverse client base. Successfully generated back-end programming utilizing Laravel framework.

Software Engineer

Space-O Technologies | August 2022 – November 2022

Generate Restful API with swagger documentation. Also build small frontend-backend modules.

Automation Architecture

Tax Tech India Pvt. Ltd. | December 2022 – Present

Develop automated software or tool using selenium and java programming. Also Test automation skills and knowledge of automated test tools for online applications e.g. Selenium.

DHRUV PATEL

Automation Architecture

T+91 6353284679 ☑ dnp176@gmail.com





Projects

Tax Calculation: Build tax calculation software backend using java backend. Also use JSP-Servlet technology. Integrate third party crypto API. Also use payment gateway system in application.

Leave Management System: Online LMS is a Web Based Application that is Developed Using PHP and MySql. The Main Purpose of LMS is to Reduced Paper Work and also Reduce The Human Work.

http://spuep.co.in/

Internship

Organization:PentagonSpace(Bangalore)

Duration: feb 2022 – july 2022

Description: It Was a Six-Month Online Internship Program Where I Was Trained In PYTHON. I Familiar With Python Full Stack Development Course. Also Provide Good Knowledge of Html, Css, Javascript, MySql Database, Django Framework and REST API.

Organization: Cad Desk India **Duration**: jan 2021 – feb 2021

Description: It Was a One-Month Online Internship Program Where I Was Trained In PYTHON. I Familiar With Python GUI Tkinter, Pyqt5 as Well as Create Some Hacking Tool.

Professional Skills

- Spring Boot
- ➤ Jsp & Servlets
- Mysql
- Php
- Core Java
- **Bug Hunting**

- ➤ Hibernate
- > Javascript
- ➤ Html5
- Css3
- > Spring MVC
- Python

- Data Science & Visualization
- Numpy & Pandas

Certificates

Cyber Security

Cisco Networking Academy

Ethical Hacking Training

Master of Project Academy

Html5 & Css3

LearnVern

Java Programming

Udemy

Networking

Udemy